realhitz4u.com 2013-11-27

# RealHitz4u Manual Traffic Exchange

**THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT DISCLOSES THE PRIVACY PRACTICES FOR RealHitz4u**

**Information Collection and Use of Information**  
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give his contact information (email address). This information is used to contact the user about the service and products we provide or wish to provide. We will not sell, share, or rent personal information to others. You can expect to receive roughly 12 emails from us per month

**Security**  
This website takes every precaution to protect our users personal information. When a user submits sensitive information via our site, the information is protected both online and off-line. Only the administrator of this site can access personal information of the users. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
If a users personally identifiable information changes, we provide a way to correct that users personal data provided to us. This can be done within the member area.

**Right to Cancel**  
Our users can cancel membership and be removed from all newsletters and databases. To do this a link is provided at the end of system generated email messages from RealHitz4u, click the link and you will be taken to a web page where you may choose to be removed from just newsletters or the entire database.

**Refund Policy**  
Satisfaction is guaranteed. If your not happy with our any of our procucts or services then you have the right to ask for a full refund within 30 days from the time of purchase.

**Site and Service Updates**  
We may send the user site and service announcement updates. We communicate with the users to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their accounts via email. We may also include promotions of 3-rd party products or services. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our Privacy statement we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner
